export let questions = [
    {
        question: "../assets/images/flags/gr.svg",
        choice1: "Italy",
        choice2: "Greece",
        choice3: "France",
        choice4: "Paraguay",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "../assets/images/flags/be.svg",
        choice1: "Germany",
        choice2: "Spain",
        choice3: "Netherlands",
        choice4: "Belgium",
        answer: 4  
    },
    {
        question: "../assets/images/flags/ca.svg",
        choice1: "Canada",
        choice2: "Peru",
        choice3: "Mexico",
        choice4: "Kenya",
        answer: 1  
    },
    {
        question: "../assets/images/flags/co.svg",
        choice1: "Equador",
        choice2: "Colombia",
        choice3: "Chile",
        choice4: "Venezuela",
        answer: 2  
    },
    {
        question: "../assets/images/flags/cz.svg",
        choice1: "Austria",
        choice2: "Slovakia",
        choice3: "Chech Republic",
        choice4: "Lithuania",
        answer: 3  
    },
    {
        question: "../assets/images/flags/pe.svg",
        choice1: "Uruguay",
        choice2: "Brazi",
        choice3: "Argentina",
        choice4: "Peru",
        answer: 4  
    },
    {
        question: "../assets/images/flags/pl.svg",
        choice1: "Poland",
        choice2: "Indonesia",
        choice3: "Sweden",
        choice4: "Lebanon",
        answer: 1  
    },
    {
        question: "../assets/images/flags/ly.svg",
        choice1: "Liberia",
        choice2: "Switzerland",
        choice3: "Taiwan",
        choice4: "Libya",
        answer: 4  
    },
    {
        question: "../assets/images/flags/sr.svg",
        choice1: "Thailand",
        choice2: "Togo",
        choice3: "Suriname",
        choice4: "Honduras",
        answer: 3  
    },
    {
        question: "../assets/images/flags/ng.svg",
        choice1: "Nigeria",
        choice2: "Nicaragua",
        choice3: "Malaysia",
        choice4: "Kenya",
        answer: 1  
    }
];